(Leonard:)...is the willingness
to recognize one's mistakes.
Madam Curie's discovery of radium
turned out to have great potential...
(Leonard:)...even though she would later die a slow,
painful death from radiation poisoning.
(Leonard:)Another example,
from the field of Ebola research..."
(Scene:)Leonard.
(Penny:)Yeah?
(Penny(hugs him):)We're okay.
LEONARD: Six two-inch dowels?
- Check.
- One package Philips head screws?
(Penny:)Guys, seriously, I grew up
on a farm, okay?
(Penny:)I rebuilt a tractor engine
when I was, like, 12.
(Penny:)I think I can put together
a cheap Swedish media center.
(Leonard:)Please, we insist.
It's the least we can do, considering...
(Sheldon:)Considering what?
(Sheldon:)How great this place looks?